LOGAN COLLINS

Senior Back-End Developer

\ +1-516-654-4426

@ hermes8527@gmail.com

EXPERIENCE

Senior Full Stack Blockchain Developer

Brewlabs

= 04/2023 - 03/2024

Phttps://brewlabs.info/

- Created the company landing page using React from the Figma design, featuring simple yet elegant components and smooth animations
- Developed a bot to fetch cryptocurrency assets and price history to show in the TradingView Chart
- Worked in the NFT Marketplace backend project to retrieve NFT sale and metadata

Senior Full Stack Blockchain Developer

SparkWorld*

= 04/2022 - 03/2023

- Led a team of four back-end developers to develop the back-end APIs to add, update and retrieve sale data in NFT Marketplace using the testdriven development approach
- Developed a bot to get NFT sale data and metadata from other NFT Marketplaces on Avalanche and store them in MongoDB as a subproject of NFT Aggregator
- Developed RESTful APIs to show NFT sale data in specific periods and find appropriate NFTs with specific prices, attributes and names

Senior Full Stack Blockchain Developer

Satang Technologies

= 04/2020 - 03/2022

- Worked in company landing page project to provide APIs to get service and product list
- Designed and developed Firo Bridge to synchronize data between the Firo chain and FiroVM chain and store transaction data in PostgreSQL database to enable Smart Contracts on Firo like Ethereum
- Took part in the Asset Tokenizer project as a back-end developer.
 Collaborated with Smart Contract and front-end team to provide APIs for uploading real-estate data on storage service and get asset and sale data

Senior Full Stack Developer

Polisport

= 04/2019 - 03/2020

https://polisport.com/, https://polisportvirtualtour.com/

- Joined the company as a Full Stack Web Developer
- Worked in backend team to retrieve products and services data to show in landing page and product lists page and provided Swagger documentation for my APIs
- · Wrote unit test scripts for the back-end APIs using Mocha and Chai
- Led Polisport Virtual Tour Project and designed backend APIs to get product and room info to show in virtual tour website

Full Stack Developer

Canary Technologies

= 04/2016 - 03/2019

- During my six-month internship as a developer, I gained valuable insights into the company's culture and development methodologies
- In the Glassboro Rentals project, I worked with two backend developers to design a MySQL database and write queries to retrieve data for the frontend
- Designed a MySQL database and contributed to three pages using Laravel framework as a Full Stack Developer in the Ventano project

SUMMARY

A seasoned back-end developer with 8+ years of experience in the web development industry. What sets me apart is the ability to learn new technologies, passion for the product and keen eye for detail.

I always create detailed workflows, progress stepby-step, and conduct thorough testing to ensure accuracy and timely development.

I enjoy proposing new ideas, wearing different hats, and collaborating with others to achieve success.

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Computer Science

GPA

DePaul Unversity

3.9 / 4.0

SKILLS

Frameworks			
Node.js	Nest.js	Larav	el
Languages			
JavaScript	TypeS	cript	Golang
3rd party libraries			
Stripe	PayPal	OAuth2	<u> </u>
Communication			
RESTful Al	Pl Webs	Socket	GraphQL
Database			
MongoDB MySQL PostgreSQL			
Development & Operations			

Development o operation

Scrum Agile

Version Control Systems

Git GitHub GitLab Bitbucket

Cloud Services

AWS GCP Microsoft Azure